Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Essex County Court Archives
University of Virginia Library
- Volume 1
  - Deposition of Lydia Nichols & Margaret Knight v. John Willard, ecca1248
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 248.
  - Deposition of Samuel Wilkins v. John Willard, ecca1249
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 249.
  - Deposition of Thomas Bailey v. John Willard, ecca1250
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 250.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Bailey v. John Willard, ecca1251
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 251.
  - Testimony of Rebecca Wilkins v. John Willard, ecca1252
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 252.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & Edward Putnam v. John Willard, ecca1253
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 253.
  - Deposition of Henry Wilkins Sr., v. John Willard, ecca1254
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 254.
  - Testimony of Benjamin Wilkins & Thomas Flint v. John Willard, ecca1255
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 255.
  - Deposition of Philip Knight & Thomas Nichols v. John Willard, ecca1256
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 256.
  - Testimony of Benjamin Wilkins & John Putnam v. John Willard and Sarah Buckley, ecca1257
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 257.
  - Deposition of Bray Wilkins v. John Willard, ecca1258
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 258.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. John Willard, ecca1259
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 259.
  - Indictment of Ann Pudeator, for Afflicting Mary Warren, ecca1260
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 260.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Alice Parker & Ann Pudeator, ecca1261
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 261.
  - Testimony of Sarah Churchill v. Ann Pudeator and Testimony of Mary Warren v. Bridget Bishop, Elizabeth Cary, George Jacobs Sr., & Ann Pudeator., ecca1262
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 262.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Alice Parker & Ann Pudeator, ecca1263
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 263.
  - Examination of Ann Pudeator, ecca1264
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 264.
  - Testimony of Sarah Churchill, Mary Warren, Elizabeth Hubbard, Ann Putnam Jr., Sarah Bibber & Mary Walcott v. Ann Pudeator, ecca1265
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 265.
  - Testimony of Samuel Pickworth and Statement of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Ann Pudeator, ecca1266
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 266.
  - Petition of Ann Pudeator, ecca1267
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 267.
  - Testimony of John Best Sr. v. Ann Pudeator, ecca1268
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 268.
  - Testimony of John Best Jr., v. Ann Pudeator, ecca1269
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 269.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Daniel Andrew, George Jacobs Jr., Rebecca Jacobs, Sarah Buckley & Mary Whittredge, ecca1270
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 270.
  - Indictment of Rebecca Jacobs, for Covenanting (Returned Ignoramus), ecca1271
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 271.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Rebecca Jacobs, ecca1272
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 272.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Roger Toothaker, ecca1273
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 273.
  - Mittimus for Roger Toothaker, John Willard, Thomas Farrar, & Elizabeth Hart, ecca1274
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 274.
  - Deposition of Thomas Gage v. Roger Toothaker, ecca1275
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 275.
  - Complaint of John Putnam Jr. & Benjamin Hutchinson v. Mary Esty, with Warrant for the Apprehension of Mary Esty, ecca1276
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 276.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Mary Esty, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1277
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 277.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Mary Esty, for Afflicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1278
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 278.
  - Deposition of Jonathan Putnamm; Samuel Braybrook, James Darling & Benjamin Hutchinson v. Mary Esty, ecca1279
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 279.
  - Testimony of George Herrick & John Putnam Jr. v. Mary Esty, ecca1280
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 280.
  - Examination of Mary Esty, ecca1281
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 281.
  - Statement of Sarah Bibber v. Mary Esty, ecca1282
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 282.
  - Statement of Mary Warren v. Mary Esty, ecca1283
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 283.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Mary Esty, ecca1284
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 284.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Mary Esty, John Willard, and Mary Whittredge, ecca1285
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 285.
  - Deposition of Abigail Williams & Ann Putnam Jr. v. Mary Esty, John Willard & Mary Whittredge and Testimony of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Mary Esty, ecca1286
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 286.
  - Excuse of Mary Towne, ecca1287
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 287.
  - Summons of Mary Towne & Rebecca Towne, ecca1288
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 288.
  - Statement of Thomas & Elizabeth Fosse for Mary Esty, ecca1289
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 289.
  - Deposition of Samuel Abby and Testimony of Sarah Trask v. Mary Esty, John Willard, & Mary Whittredge, ecca1290
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 290.
  - Deposition of Edward Putnam v. Mary Esty, ecca1291
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 291.
  - Deposition of Samuel Smith v. Mary Esty, ecca1292
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 292.
  - Deposition of Margaret Reddington v. Mary Esty, ecca1293
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 293.
  - Petition of Mary Esty, ecca1294
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 294.
  - Petition of Sarah Cloyce & Mary Esty, ecca1295
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 295.
  - Statements of John & Mary Arnold for Mary Esty & Sarah Cloyce, ecca1296
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 296.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam v. Sarah Procter, ecca1297
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 297.
  - Testimony of John Putnam Jr. v. Sarah Procter, ecca1298
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 298.
  - Deposition of David Ferneaux & Jonathan Walcott Jr. v. Sarah Procter, ecca1299
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 299.
  - Complaint of Thomas Putnam & John Putnam v. Sarah Procter, Sarah Bassett, & Susannah Roots, ecca1300
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 300.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth v. Sarah Procter, John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1301
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 301.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth v. Sarah Procter, Mary De Rich, John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1302
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 302.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Sarah Procter, ecca1303
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 303.
  - Statement of Susannah Shelden v. Sarah Procter, Daniel Andrew, George Jacobs Jr., & Phillip English, ecca1304
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 304.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Susannah Roots, ecca1305
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 305.
  - Statement of Andrew Elliott v. Susannah Roots, ecca1306
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 306.
  - Complaint of Nathaniel Ingersoll & Thomas Rayment v. Benjamin Procter, Mary DeRich & Sarah Pease, ecca1307
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 307.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Benjamin Procter, Mary DeRich & Sarah Pease, ecca1308
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 308.
  - Complaint of Joseph Houlton & John Walcott v. Martha Carrier, Elizabeth Fosdick, Wilmot Redd, Sarah Rice, Elizabeth How, John Alden, William Procter, John Flood, Mary Toothaker, Margaret Toothaker, & Arthur Abbot., ecca1309
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 309.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Martha Carrier, ecca1310
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 310.
  - Examination of Martha Carrier, ecca1311
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 311.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Martha Carrier, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1312
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 312.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Martha Carrier, ecca1313
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 313.
  - Testimony of Benjamin Abbott and Deposition of Sarah Abbott v. Martha Carrier, ecca1314
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 314.
  - Deposition of John Rogers v. Martha Carrier, ecca1315
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 315.
  - Deposition of Phoebe Chandler and Testimony of Bridget Chandler v. Martha Carrier, ecca1316
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 316.
  - Deposition of Allen Toothaker v. Martha Carrier, ecca1317
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 317.
  - Statement of Samuel Preston v. Martha Carrier, ecca1318
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 318.
  - Statement of Francis Dane Sr., Regarding Some of the Andover Acccused, ecca1319
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 319.
  - Witnesses v. Elizabeth How, ecca1320
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 320.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Elizabeth How, ecca1321
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 321.
  - Examination of Elizabeth How, ecca1322
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 322.
  - Deposition of Timothy Perley & Deborah Perley v. Elizabeth How, ecca1323
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 323.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Elizabeth How, for Afflicting Mary Walcott, ecca1324
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 324.
  - Deposition of Samuel Perley & Ruth Perley v. Elizabeth How and List of Witnesses v. Elizabeth How, ecca1325
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 325.
  - Testimony of Samuel Phillips & Edward Payson for Elizabeth How, ecca1326
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 326.
  - Deposition of Deborah Hadley for Elizabeth How, ecca1327
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 327.
  - Testimony of Simon Chapman & Mary Chapman for Elizabeth How, ecca1328
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 328.
  - Statement of Daniel Warner, John Warner & Sarah Warner for Elizabeth How, ecca1329
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 329.
  - Deposition of Isaac Cummings Sr. v. Elizabeth How, ecca1330
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 330.
  - Three Depositions of Mary Cummings v. Elizabeth How., ecca1331
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 331.
  - Statement of Joseph Knowlton & Mary Knowlton for Elizabeth How, ecca1332
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 332.
  - Testimony of Isaac Cummings Jr. v. Elizabeth How, ecca1333
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 333.
  - Testimony of Francis Lane v. Elizabeth How, ecca1334
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 334.
  - Testimony of John How v. Elizabeth How, ecca1335
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 335.
  - Deposition of Jacob Foster v. Elizabeth How, ecca1336
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 336.
  - Deposition of Joseph Safford v. Elizabeth How & Bridget Bishop, ecca1337
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 337.
  - Deposition of Thomas Andrews v. Elizabeth How, ecca1338
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 338.
  - Statement of James How Sr., for Elizabeth How, ecca1339
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 339.
  - Deposition of Priscilla Chub v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1400
    W. Elliot Woodward, Records of Salem Witchcraft, Copied from ther Original Documents., 2 vols. (Privately printed, Roxbury, MA: 1864) Vol. I, pp. 177-78.
- Volume 2
  - Indictment of William Procter, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard (Returned Ignoramus), ecca2001
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 1.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of William Procter, ecca2002
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 2.
  - Indictment of William Procter, for Afflicting Mary Warren (Returned Ignoramus), ecca2003
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 3.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. William Procter, ecca2004
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 4.
  - Indictment of Wilmot Redd, for Afflicting Elizabeth Booth (Returned Ignoramus), ecca2005
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 5.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Wilmot Redd, ecca2006
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 6.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2007
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 7.
  - Examination of Wilmot Redd, ecca2008
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 8.
  - Indictment of Wilmot Redd, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca2009
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 9.
  - Deposition of Mary Warren v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2010
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 10.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2011
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 11.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2012
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 12.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2013
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 13.
  - Testimony of Charity Pitman v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2014
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 14.
  - Statements of Sarah Dodd & Ambrose Gale v. Wilmot Redd, ecca2015
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 15.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Elizabeth Fosdick & Elizabeth Paine, ecca2016
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 16.
  - Complaint of Nathaniel Putnam, Peter Whipple & Peter Tufts v. Elizabeth Fosdick & Elizabeth Paine, ecca2017
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 17.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Mary Ireson, ecca2018
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 18.
  - Complaint of Edward Putnam, Thomas Rayment, Elizabeth Booth, Abigail Williams & Ann Putnam v. Mary Ireson, ecca2019
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 19.
  - Summons for Witness v. George Burroughs, ecca2021
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 21.
  - Testimony of Samuel Webber v. George Burroughs, ecca2022
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 22.
  - Physical Examination of George Burroughs & George Jacobs Sr., ecca2023
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 23.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. George Burroughs and Declaration of Thomas Putnam, Peter Prescott, Robert Morrell & Ezekiel Cheevers v. George Burroughs, ecca2024
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 24.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. George Burroughs and Declaration by Thomas Putnam & Edward Putnam v. George Burroughs, ecca2025
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 25.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. George Burroughs; Declaration of Edward Putnam & Thomas Putnam v. George Burroughs, ecca2026
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 26.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. George Burroughs, ecca2027
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 27.
  - Depositions of Simon Willard v. George Burroughs; Testimony of William Wormall v. George Burroughs, ecca2028
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 28.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. George Burroughs, ecca2029
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 29.
  - Statement of Elizabeth Hubbard v. George Burroughs, ecca2030
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 30.
  - Fragment of the Examination of Deliverance Hobbs, ecca2031
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 31.
  - Deposition of Hannah Harris v. George Burroughs, ecca2032
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 32.
  - Deposition of Thomas Greenslit v. George Burroughs, ecca2033
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 33.
  - Statement of Susannah Shelden v. George Burroughs, ecca2034
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 34.
  - Statement of Benjamin Hutchinson v. George Burroughs, ecca2035
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 35.
  - Memorandum: Major Brown, Thomas Evans, Thomas Ruck, Martha Tyler & Sarah Wilson Jr. v. George Burroughs, ecca2036
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 36.
  - Indictment of Abigail Faulkner Sr., for Afflicting Sarah Phelps Jr., ecca2037
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 37.
  - Indictment of Abigail Faulkner Sr. for Afflicting Martha Sprague, ecca2038
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 38.
  - Deposition of Rose Foster v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2039
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 39.
  - Examinations of Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2040
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 40.
  - Deposition of Martha Sprague v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2041
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 41.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2042
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 42.
  - Deposition of Mary Warren v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2043
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 43.
  - Deposition of Sarah Phelps v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2044
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 44.
  - Summary of the Examinations of Dorothy Faulkner, Abigail Faulkner Jr., Martha Tyler, Johannah Tyler, Sarah Wilson Jr., & Joseph Draper v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2045
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 45.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Abigail Faulkner Sr., ecca2046
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 46.
  - Indictment of Ann Foster, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca2047
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 47.
  - Examination of Ann Foster, ecca2048
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 48.
  - Indictment of Mary Lacey Sr., for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca2049
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 49.
  - Depositions of Elizabeth Hubbard, Mercy Lewis & Mary Warren v. Mary Lacey Sr., ecca2050
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 50.
  - Examination of Mary Lacey Sr., ecca2051
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 51.
  - Examination of Rebecca Eames, ecca2052
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 52.
  - Indictment of Rebecca Eames, for Afflicting Timothy Swan, ecca2053
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 53.
  - Indictment of Rebecca Eames, for Covenanting, ecca2054
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 54.
  - Indictment of Samuel Wardwell, for Covenanting, ecca2055
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 55.
  - Indictment of Samuel Wardwell, for Afflicting Martha Sprague, ecca2056
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 56.
  - Depositions of Martha Sprague, Mary Walcott & Mary Warren v. Samuel Wardwell, ecca2057
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 57.
  - Deposition of Ephraim Foster v. Samuel Wardwell, ecca2058
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 58.
  - Examination of Samuel Wardwell, ecca2059
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 59.
  - Deposition of Thomas Chandler v. Samuel Wardwell, ecca2060
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 60.
  - Deposition of Joseph Ballard v. Samuel Wardwell, ecca2061
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 61.
  - Deposition of Abigail Martin & John Bridges v. Samuel Wardwell, ecca2062
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 62.
  - Examination of Mary Parker, ecca2063
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 63.
  - Indictment of Mary Parker, for Afflicting Martha Sprague (Returned Ignoramus), ecca2064
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 64.
  - Testimony of Samuel Shattuck v. Alice Parker, ecca2065
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 65.
  - Deposition of John Westgate v. Alice Parker, ecca2066
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 66.
  - Testimony of John Bullock & Martha Dutch v. Alice Parker, ecca2067
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 67.
  - Statements of William Barker Jr. & Mercy Wardwell v. Mary Parker, ecca2068
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 68.
  - Indictment of Mary Bradbury, for Afflicting Timothy Swan, ecca2069
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 69.
  - Indictment of Mary Bradbury, for Afflicting Sarah Bibber, ecca2070
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 70.
  - Statement of George Herrick v. Mary Bradbury, Sarah Rice, Wilmot Redd, & Elizabeth Fosdick, ecca2071
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 71.
  - Plea of Mary Bradbury, ecca2072
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 72.
  - Testimony of Thomas Bradbury for Mary Bradbury, ecca2073
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 73.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2074
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 74.
  - Testimony of James Allen, Robert Pike & John Pike for Mary Bradbury, ecca2075
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 75.
  - Deposition of Samuel Endicott v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2076
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 76.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2077
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 77.
  - Deposition of Mary Warren v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2078
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 78.
  - Deposition of James Carr v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2079
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 79.
  - Deposition of Richard Carr & Zerubable Endicott v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2080
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 80.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Mary Bradbury, ecca2081
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 81.
  - Deposition of William Carr for Mary Bradbury, ecca2082
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 82.
  - Petition in Support of Mary Bradbury, ecca2083
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 83.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Giles Cory, ecca2084
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 84.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. Giles Cory, ecca2085
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 85.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Giles Cory, ecca2086
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 86.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Giles Cory, ecca2087
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 87.
  - Deposition of Benjamin Gould v. Giles Cory, Martha Cory, & John Procter, ecca2088
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 88.
  - Statements of Mary Warren, Elizabeth Woodwell, Mary Walcott & Elizabeth Hubbard v. Giles Cory, ecca2089
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 89.
  - Statement of Susannah Shelden v. Giles Cory, Elizabeth Procter, Sarah Buckley, & John Willard, ecca2090
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 90.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth & Alice Booth v. Giles Cory, ecca2091
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 91.
  - Testimony of John DeRich v. Giles Cory; Declaration of Hannah Small & Martha Adams v. Giles Cory, ecca2092
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 92.
  - Testimony of Martha Dutch v. Alice Parker, ecca2093
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 93.
  - Deposition of Frances Wycomb v. Margaret Scott, ecca2094
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 94.
  - Testimony of Philip & Sarah Nelson v. Margaret Scott, ecca2095
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 95.
  - Petition of the Selectmen of Andover, Regarding the Children of Samuel Wardwell, ecca2096
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 96.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & William Murray v. Alice Parker, ecca2097
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 97.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Lydia Dustin, ecca2098
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 98.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Dustin, ecca2099
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 99.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Ann Sears, Bethiah Carter Sr. & Bethiah Carter Jr., ecca2100
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 100.
  - Examination of Deliverance Hobbs, ecca2101
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 101.
  - Examination of Deliverance Hobbs in Prison, ecca2102
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 102.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Abigail Soames, ecca2103
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 103.
  - Warrant No. 1 for the Apprehension of Elizabeth Colson, ecca2104
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 104.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Mary DeRich, ecca2105
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 105.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Pease, ecca2106
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 106.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of John Alden, ecca2107
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 107.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Rice, ecca2108
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 108.
  - Complaint of Thomas Putnam & Benjamin Hutchinson v. Elizabeth Cary, ecca2109
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 109.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Ann Dolliver, ecca2110
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 110.
  - Examination of Richard Carrier, ecca2111
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 111.
  - Statement of Sarah Ingersoll & Ann Andrews Regarding Sarah Churchill, ecca2113
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 113.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., Thomas Putnam & Robert Morrell v. Thomas Farrer, ecca2114
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 114.
  - Testimony of Elizabeth Nicholason v. Ann Dolliver, ecca2115
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 115.
  - Deposition of James Kettle v. Sarah Bishop, ecca2116
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 116.
  - Statement of Mary Warren v. Mary Ireson & Mary Toothaker, ecca2117
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 117.
  - Testimony of John DeRich v. Margaret Jacobs, ecca2118
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 118.
  - Testimony of John Porter & Lydia Porter Regarding Sarah Bibber, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2119
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 119.
  - Testimony of Joseph Fowler Regarding Sarah Bibber, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2120
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 120.
  - Testimony of Thomas Jacobs & Mary Jacobs Regarding Sarah Bibber, in Support of Rebecca Nurse; Testimony of Richard Walker Regarding Sarah Bibber, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2121
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 121.
  - Deposition of Clement Coldum Regarding Elizabeth Hubbard, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2122
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 122.
  - Testimony of James Kettle Regarding Elizabeth Hubbard, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2123
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 123.
  - Deposition of Nathaniel & Hannah Ingersoll v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca2124
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 124.
  - Testimony of John Putnam Sr. & Rebecca Putnam for Rebecca Nurse, ecca2125
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 125.
  - Deposition of Hannah Welch v. William Hobbs, ecca2126
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 126.
  - Deposition of Benjamin Wilkins, John Wilkins & Nathaniel Richardson v. John Willard, ecca2127
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 127.
  - Testimony of Robert Moulton Regarding Susannah Shelden, in Support of Rebecca Nurse, ecca2128
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 128.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Abraham Perkins, Innkeeper, ecca2129
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 129.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Thomas Manning, Blacksmith, ecca2130
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 130.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Nathaniel Ingersoll, Innkeeper, ecca2131
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 131.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Joseph Fuller, Constable, ecca2132
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 132.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by Isaac Little & John Harris, Sheriff's Deputy, ecca2133
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 133.
  - Census of Prisoners in Salem & Boston Prisons, ecca2134
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 134.
  - docketed Cover Paper Used to Contain the Warrant for the Execution of Sarah Good, Elizabeth How, Susannah Martin, Rebecca Nurse, & Sarah Wilds., ecca2135
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 135.
  - Reversal of Attainder of George Burroughs et al., ecca2136
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 136.
  - Account for Payment Submitted by William Starling, Constable, ecca2137
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 137.
  - Order for Payment of Damages by Governor Joseph Dudley, ecca2138
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 138.
  - Request for Copy of Act for Restitution, ecca2139
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 139.
  - Receipts for Sums Paid in Restitution, ecca2140
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 140.
  - Summary of Receipts of the Relations & Sufferers, ecca2141
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 141.
  - Order of William Good for Payment, Cases of Sarah and Dorothy Good, ecca2142
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 142.
  - Summary of the Amounts Requested by the Victims & Their Relatives, ecca2143
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 143.
  - Order of Elizabeth Very for Payment, Cases of John & Elizabeth Procter, ecca2144
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 144.
  - Order of Nathaniel Gowing for Payment, Cases of John & Elizabeth Procter, ecca2145
    ECCA, Vol. 2, no. 145.